你这是在干嘛
What-what are you doing?
红灯了  所以我停下啊
The light is red so I came to a stop.
你开着偷来的警车  后车厢还有死掉的妓女
You're in a stolen cop car with a dead hooker in the trunk.
你不必遵守交通规则吧
You don't have to obey traffic laws.
我知道我不必
I know I don't have to.
但选择遵守才是乐趣所在啊
The fun is choosing to.
你们没有来学院聚会啊
Hey. Missed you guys at the faculty mixer.
真应该来的  甜点简直香蕉你个芭乐赞
Ah, you should have been there; dessert was bananas.
抱歉  这话有点歧义  甜点是派
Sorry, that was misleading. The dessert was pie,
这个派香蕉你个大西瓜赞
but the pie was bananas.
其实这个派是樱桃口味
Actually, the pie was cherry,
但吃起来这美味简直香蕉你个大樱桃
but the taste of the pie was... bananas.
这些聚会根本就是在浪费大学的钱
Those mixers are such a waste of university money.
如果学校少把钱花在
If they spent less money
这些琐碎的狗屁上  多花钱在科学上
on frivolous nonsense and more money on science,
对大家都有好处
we'd all be better off.
你就是个理论物理学家
You're a theoretical physicist.
除了一个办公室跟一张白板  你还需要什么
What more do you need than an office and a whiteboard?
某一天  我的量子退相干导致熵减少的
Someday, my new formulas on entropy decrease
新公式将会需要测试
due to quantum decoherence will need to be tested
到时候就会需要资金
and that will require funding.
你的理论都挺抽象的
Your theories are pretty abstract.
我都不知道该怎么
I wouldn't even know how to
设计出证明它们的实验
design an experiment to prove them.
某实验物理学家如是说
Says the experimental physicist.
我知道大学可以从哪里削减支出了
Well, I know a place the university can make some cuts.
莱纳德  拜拜了您那
Bye, Leonard.
慢着  慢着
One second, one second.
他说的不无道理啊
He's got a point.
要想证实你的弦理论研究
In order to corroborate your string theory research,
你就得制造出一个黑洞
you'd have to create a black hole.
那不会毁掉地球吗
Wouldn't that destroy the Earth?
或许吧  但大家都可以知道我是对的再入土
Perhaps, but we'd all go to the grave knowing I was right.
我想或许你可以制造个微型黑洞啊
I guess you could create a contained microscopic black hole.
有意思
Huh. Interesting.
欢迎回来  莱纳德
Welcome back, Leonard.
抱歉  你得卷铺盖了
Sorry, you're out.
我做什么了
What did I do?
正是如此
Exactly.
第十一季  第二十二集
这个好好看
Ooh, this one's pretty.
我妈不会同意
Mm. My mother wouldn't approve;
露太多锁骨了
shows too much clavicle.
她把锁骨称为"胸部的迎宾脚踏垫"
She calls it "The bosom's welcome mat."
我真是等不及要喝醉
I can't wait to get drunk
然后在婚礼上跟她起争执了
and pick a fight with her at your wedding.
真的好难知道到底哪件我穿起来会好看
It's just so hard to tell what will look good on me.
不  这只是让你知道个方向
No. This is just to give you ideas.
让你知道你是想要简单高雅款呢
You know, do-do you want something simple and elegant?
你想要拖尾[火车]吗
I mean, do you want a train?
大家在聊火车啊
Ooh, we're talking about trains.
不是你喜欢的那种火车
Not the kind of trains you like.
我喜欢所有火车啊  蒸汽火车  柴油火车
Oh, I like all kinds of trains-- steam, diesel,
煤炭火车  高架列车  子弹列车
coal, elevated, bullet.
你有本事就说出个我不喜欢的火车
I defy you to name a train that I don't like.
在婚纱后面的那种火车[拖尾]
The kind on the back of a wedding dress?
我完全没料到这个  你厉害
I did not see that coming. Good job.
趁我们刚好在聊有关时尚的话题
But while we're on the subject of fashion,
我明天想跟大学要研究资金
I'm asking the university for some funding tomorrow.
我应该穿什么
What should I wear?
我有一件聚拢提升型胸罩可以借你穿
Mm. Well, I've got a push-up bra I can loan you
它总能让我得到免费酒水
that always gets me free drinks.
你想要多少经费
How much money are you asking for?
5亿
$500 million.
那我劝你直接不穿胸罩去吧
Then I'd go no bra.
你要这么大一笔钱干什么啊
What do you need that kind of money for?
我想出了一个实验设计
I have figured out an experimental design
可以证实我最新的弦理论想法
that may corroborate my latest thinking on string theory.
我只需要2148台大功率激光器
I just need 2,148 high-power lasers
来把20微克的黄金压缩到足够小的质量
to compress 20 micrograms of gold into a small enough volume
从而创造出一个微型黑洞
to make a microscopic black hole.
点头就好了
Just nod.
谢尔顿  他们不会给你5亿的
Sheldon, they're not gonna give you half a billion dollars.
连我都要不到那么多
I mean, they won't even give me that much
我可是保证了我能让人的大脑"返老还童"呢
and I keep promising I can make people's brains "grow younger."
你能吗
Can you?
不能
No. Shh.
但我需要啊  这是唯一有办法解决
But I need it. It's the only way to settle the contradictions
重力与量子力学间矛盾的方法了
between gravity and quantum mechanics.
这要求的款项太大笔了  你不能一次要这么多
Well, it's too much money, you can't ask for that all at once.
那我让他们分6期付款如何
Well, what if I ask for it in six easy installments
每次给8333万3333.33
of $83,333,333.33?
好吧  那你去要个2千万如何
Okay. What if you asked for $20 million?
抱歉  我是要做科学研究
I'm sorry, I'm trying to do science,
不是要请嘎嘎小姐来我生日表演
not hire Lady Gaga to come to my birthday.
你知道人家嘎嘎小姐[歌手]是谁吗
Do you even know who Lady Gaga is?
我推断她应该是嘎嘎先生的老婆
Presumably, the wife of Lord Gaga.
谢尔顿  其实佩妮说的有道理
Sheldon, you know, Penny's got a point.
有时候你想跟别人提一个大要求
Sometimes when you want something big from someone,
你得小心别一下就把别人给吓跑  懂吗
you-you got to be careful not to scare them away, you know?
你得小火开始  慢慢加料慢慢炖
You got to start small and-and build up slowly,
哪怕得炖他个足足八年
even if it takes eight years.
八个漫长的年头
Eight long years.
年数莫名精确啊
That's oddly specific.
你做过这件事吗
Have you ever done that?
没有
Nope.
用这个程度的大功率激光器阵列
So with this level of high-power laser array,
我们终于可以有办法
we would actually be able to solve
一劳永逸地解决黑洞信息悖论呢
the black hole information paradox once and for all.
非常出色  那你需要多少研究资金呢
That's impressive, and how much funding were you looking for?
2千万
$20 million.
真的吗
Really?
你觉得你用2千万就能造出来吗
You think you can build that for $20 million?
下辈子吧
Not a chance.
抱歉  那你为什么跟我要这数目
I'm sorry, then why are you asking me for it?
因为一旦你已经花了2千万
Because once you've spent $20 million,
你就很有可能再给我追加5千万
you're much more likely to give me an additional 50.
所以其实你的意思是  只要有7千万
So actually, what you're saying is with $70 million,
你就能造出这个
you can build this.
我能理解您为何这么想  但非也
I can see why you'd think that, but no.
你肯定不能去跟董事会的人说
You can't go to the board of trustees
你给了谢尔顿·库珀7千万美元
and say you gave Sheldon Cooper $70 million
但什么能拿出来的成果都没有
and have nothing to show for it.
不能  你唯一保留颜面的方法就是再加一倍
No. The only way you'd be able to save face is to double down.
所以就是1亿4千万
So 140?
然后还得再加倍
And then double again.
2亿8千万吗
280?
然后有个好消息  再将近双倍一次
And then-- good news-- not quite double again.
所以...  您怎么说
So, uh, what do you say?
我们说好了吗
We have a deal?
他拒绝了吗
He said no?
"不要"只有两个字
No. That's only a two letter word.
你得再加倍
You're gonna have to double down.
我也很遗憾  谢尔顿  但这种事常有
Well, I'm sorry, Sheldon, but this sort of thing happens.
科学家希格斯等了足足50年
Higgs had to wait almost 50 years
他们才终于建了一个大到足以证明他理论的对撞机
before they built a collider big enough to prove his theory.
50年吗
50 years?
但我现在就想玩到它
But I want to play with it now.
你得等等  等到科学够进步了
You just have to wait for science to catch up
或者这科技技术变便宜了
or technology to get cheaper.
你想想比如DVD播放器
Think about, uh, DVD players--
以前一台要上千块钱
they used to cost, like, a thousand dollars,
但前几天我还用一台来砸扁虫子
but just the other day I used one to smash a bug.
对  你得有耐心
Yeah, you-you just have to be patient.
但要是我耐心等候时
But what if while I'm being patient,
有比我更死缠烂打的人
someone more relentless than me
逼得他们大学给他们拨款了呢
badgers their university into giving them money?
如果有人比你更死缠烂打
If there's someone more relentless than you,
我还挺想会会他们
I'd like to meet them.
我不想
I would not.
我不会坐等大学自己想通
I'm not waiting for the university to come around.
我会另找法子筹款
I'll find another way to raise the money.
如果是可以朝你丢派的那种出气小房间
Ooh, if it's one of those booths where we can throw a pie at you,
我愿意奉献20大洋
I'm in for, like, 20 bucks.
如果我能朝你丢DVD机  我愿意出40
40 bucks if I can throw a DVD player.
二位想来杯香槟吗
Would you like some champagne?
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thanks. - ?Sure.
这挺不错的
This is nice.
你是指帮艾米选婚纱还是白天买醉
What? Helping Amy find a dress or day drinking?
反正就是不错  问个屁
It's just nice, okay?
你们觉得怎么样
What do you think?
艾米  我的天啊
Amy, oh, my God.
你看起来真美
You look so beautiful.
我也觉得自己很美
I feel beautiful.
你们瞧  两边锁骨都露了
And look, both clavicles.
吃屎吧  老妈
Take that, Mom.
你知道俗语说的好
You know what they say:
有料不秀  天诛地灭
if you got 'em, flaunt 'em.
有没可能第一条就是最好的选择
Is it possible that the very first dress is the dress?
说什么傻话
Oh, don't be silly.
怎么能买你试穿的第一条裙子
You can't buy the first dress you try on.
这就跟嫁给你第一个男...
That'd be like marrying the first guy that you...
怎么能买你试穿的第一条裙子
You can't buy the first dress you try on.
还有手指三明治  这地方棒极了
Little finger sandwiches, too. This place is amazing.
手指三明治有意思的是
Interesting thing about finger sandwiches:
你把足够分量拼起来
you put enough of them together,
就能得到一个完整的三明治
you got a sandwich.
姐妹们  有个问题
Uh, guys, we have a problem.
-你没事吧  -怎么了
- Are you okay? ?- What's wrong?
我穿所有婚纱都美爆了
I look amazing in all of these dresses!
瞧瞧你的小蛮腰
Wow. Look at your waist.
你之前都藏哪儿去了
Where you been hiding that thing?
伯纳黛特别说啦
Bernadette, stop.
佩妮  轮到你开始吹捧了
Penny, you say something nice now.
天啊  谢尔顿看到你穿这条裙子后
Boy, you know, when Sheldon sees you in that dress,
一定会想井然有序地把裙子脱掉
he's gonna want to methodically take it off,
折好  小心放入储物盒
fold it up, carefully place it in a storage box,
贴好标签  然后尽情蹂躏你
label it, and then ravish you.
我要不要再试几条
Should I try on some more?
你享受这过程吗
Are you having fun?
我享受这美绝人寰的过程吗
Am I having fun being beautiful?
老娘当然享受
Of course I am!
太好了  继续
Great. Keep going.
就是它了
This is it.
这就是命中注定的裙子
This is the one.
你们爱它吗
Do you love it?
你爱吗
Do you?
我超爱啊
I do.
哇
Wow.
我也是  哇
Also, wow.
-你好  莱纳德  -嘿
- Hello, Leonard. ?- Hi.
你在忙吗
Are you doing anything?
没有  我就坐在书桌前
No. I'm just sitting here at my desk
无目的地敲打电脑键盘
typing on my computer for nothing.
我就是这么想的  但我不想想当然
That was my guess, but I didn't want to assume.
你能帮我拍摄众筹网站的短片吗
Can you help me shoot my Kickstarter video?
你真觉得大家会给你
Do you really think people are gonna give you
五亿美元吗
half a billion dollars?
当然不是  但如果我能筹到足够的种子基金
Of course not, but if I can raise enough seed money
显示出我是认真的
to show that I'm serious,
应该就能吸引到一些大款投资人
I should be able to attract some major investors.
快看看我提供的超酷捐款福利
And look at the cool incentives I'm offering.
"捐5万  我就帮你检查饮食情况
"For $50,000, I will examine your diet
为你量身定制如厕时间表"
and create a customized bathroom schedule."
挺合适的  5万丢进马桶冲走
That's fitting-- 50 grand down the toilet.
这个怎么样
Well, how about this?
捐10万  我就亲自为你家
For $100,000, I will design the flag
设计一面旗帜
of your house or apartment.
还有  捐100万
And for $1 million,
我就莅临你家告诉你  你有什么毛病
I will come over and tell you what's wrong with you.
这么多年来  我都免费"享受"这待遇
Aw, and all these years, I've been getting that for free.
少自以为是了  莱纳德
Don't be smug, Leonard.
这正是你其中一种毛病
That's one of the things that's wrong with you.
这趟行程收获颇丰
Well, that was a successful trip.
是啊
Yes.
艾米找到了中意的裙子
Amy found a dress that she liked.
确实
She sure did.
她找到了一条看上去...
She found a dress that looked like...
让她快乐的裙子
like it made her happy.
她确实看起来很快乐
She-she did look happy.
她脸上洋溢着幸福的光彩
I mean, her face was just glowing, so...
对  我们应该确保摄影师知道
Yeah, we should make sure the photographer knows
拍的时候...  尽量特写脸
to just really... get in there.
我们同意那裙子丑爆了对吧
So we agree it's awful?
那条裙子就该一把火给烧了
That dress should be set on fire!
我们该说什么吗
Should we say something?
当然不能说
No, we can't.
但她带我们一起去选裙子
But don't you think she brought us with her
不就是想听我们诚实的意见吗
'cause she wants our honest opinion?
没人想听真话
No one wants that.
我就想啊
I do.
你才不想
No, ya don't.
我不想她难看
I don't want her to look back
觉得自己犯了大错
and think she made some awful mistake.
《芝麻街》中的角色
你是说像你那个蠢兮兮的曲奇怪兽纹身一样吗
You mean like your dumb Cookie Monster tattoo?
看见没  这样好玩吗
See? Was that fun?
总会有人说难听话
Someone's gonna say something.
与其让她在婚礼上出丑  不如我们现在告诉她
It should be us now instead of everyone at her wedding.
好吧  但我们得委婉一点说
Okay, but as long as we do it gently.
还得一起说
And together.
我的裙子怎么了
Well, what about my dress?
你们不喜欢吗
Don't you like it?
-我不喜欢  -裙子太美了
- I don't. - ?It's beautiful.
斯图尔特  我想卖些漫画
Hey, Stuart, I'd like to sell some comic books.
这我太了解了
Oh. Well, I know all about that.
第一步是从被踢出艺校开始
Step one is flunk out of art school.
你为什么要卖漫画
Well, why are you selling 'em?
大学拒绝给我的实验拨款
The university is refusing to fund my experiment,
所以我需要筹钱自己做
so I need to raise money and do it on my own.
你需要多少钱
Ah. How much do you need?
一开始我想先筹50万
For a start, I'm trying to raise $500,000.
那我希望你有那超稀有的
Well, I hope you have that rare Superman
印在真正超人皮肤上的《超人》
printed on the skin of actual Superman.
我知道你在开玩笑
I know you're making a joke,
但我真的有不少期值钱的漫画
but I really do have some valuable issues in here.
这还只是第一盒  后面陆续还有
And this is just the first box of many.
好吧  看看你这儿有什么
All right, let's see what you got.
这是整套托德·麦克法兰的《再生侠》吗
Huh. Is this a complete run of Todd McFarlane's Spawn?
没错
Yes.
瞧瞧这个
Ooh, look at this.
《巨大X战警》第一期
Giant-Size X-Men number one,
当年莱恩·韦恩对《X战警》系列的承先启后之作
Len Wein's relaunch of the franchise.
我知道这是什么  是我亲手买来
Yeah. I know what it is. I'm the one who bought it,
装入袋子  放好硬纸板  并用胶带封好的
bagged it, boarded it and taped it shut
而且全程戴着棉制白手套
while wearing white cotton gloves.
好吧  你知道的
Okay, well, you know,
我需要打开看看它们是否完好
I'm gonna have to open it to assess its condition.
温柔一点
Just be gentle.
它们从来没有被男人碰过
It's never felt the touch of a man before.
感觉你并不愿意卖掉它们啊
You don't seem like you really want to sell these.
我当然不想卖
Of course I don't want to sell these.
它们是我的珍宝
These are all important to me,
但还是比不上科学
but not as important as science,
若为科学故  珍宝亦可抛
and if this is the sacrifice I need to make, then so be it.
好吧  那就把它们留在这儿
Okay. Uh, why don't you leave these here with me,
我帮你估个价
and I'll-I'll price 'em out for you.
我能站在旁边看你弄吗
Is it okay if I stand here and watch?
可以呀
Sure.
如果之后有人问起  就说我很勇敢
If anyone asks, tell them I was brave.
你刚才就这么把我出卖了吗
Hey, I can't believe you just threw me under the bus.
对啊  超不敢相信吧
I know, right? That was crazy.
你...
Well...
你这样害我成为什么人了啊
Do you know how that makes me look?
这个简单  坏人
Uh, that's an easy one-- bad. ?Well...
你为什么不告诉她你也不喜欢那裙子
Why didn't you tell her that you didn't like the dress, either?
说好的姐妹一条心呢
I mean, what happened to our united front?
不好意思  你是第一天当女人吗
I'm sorry. Is this your first day being a girl?
你妈给你做的午饭吗
Ooh, did your mom pack your lunch?
当然不是了
Of course not.
你知道从德州连夜寄来干冰包装的
Do you know how much it costs to pack a tuna fish sandwich
金枪鱼三明治要多贵吗
in dry ice and overnight it from Texas?
反正我知道  我妈说太贵了
Well, I do, and my mother says it's too expensive.
我喜欢金枪鱼
I like tuna fish.
那你想吃不  5000块卖给你
Do you want it? I'll sell it to you for $5,000.
你的募款进行得如何了
How's the fundraising going?
-看情况  拉杰  买吗  -不买
- Oh, that depends. Raj, was that a "Yes"? - ?No.
进行得不顺
It's going badly.
你现在募到多少钱了
How much have you raised?
众筹网的项目
Well, with my Kickstarter campaign,
卖掉收藏品的收入  和我的银行余额
selling my collectibles, and the money in my bank account,
差不多6万5千元
about $65,000.
已经很多了
Wow. That's a lot.
还远远不够
Yeah, not enough.
真是闹心  科学竟然沦落为
It's so frustrating that science should be held hostage
金钱的奴隶
to the almighty dollar.
别放弃得太早  你总能找到钱的
Well, don't give up. You'll find that money somewhere.
-你真这么想吗  -才怪
- You really think so? ?- No,
但他现在有了个爱好是好事
but it's good that he has a hobby.
你考虑过去维加斯吗
You ever thought of going to Vegas?
能说更详细点吗
Can you be more specific?
拉斯维加斯
Las Vegas?
你是说赌博呀
Oh, you mean gambling. ?
这个主意倒不坏
Oh. Well, that's not the worst idea.
这是最坏的主意了  就连拉杰
Um, it is the worst idea, and I'm including the year
曾经穿了一年运动服都比这个主意好
that Raj wore nothing but tracksuits.
普通人赢不了赌场
Ordinary people can't beat a casino,
但数学家和科学家
but mathematicians and scientists,
常常是赌场赢家
they do it all the time.
曾经有一群麻省理工的学生
Yeah, a group of students
从赌城赢走了几千万  这还只是麻省理工呢
from MIT took Las Vegas for millions, and that's MIT.
连霍华德都能读的学校
Howard went there.
来吧  谢尔顿
Come on, Sheldon.
我立马就送你去沙漠
I'll give you a ride out to the desert right now.
谁都不许去赌城
No one is going to Vegas.
在到沙漠里的赌城前他就被我埋了
No, we weren't gonna make it to Vegas.
你有空吗
Hi. Do you have a minute?
看情况  我穿这身还行吗
Depends. Is what I'm wearing okay,
是不是该去换身衣服呢
or should I go change first?
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry.
我不应该说不喜欢你的裙子
I never should have said I didn't like your dress.
那是你的婚礼  只要你觉得美丽
It's your wedding, and all that matters is
就够了
that you feel beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
那我们没事了吧
So, are... are we good?
不  没事才怪
No, we're not good.
你毁了我的裙子
You ruined my dress.
为什么  我都说了你可以穿
Well, why? I just said you should wear it.
我现在不能穿了  我知道你讨厌它
Well, I can't wear it now. I mean, I know you hate it.
这件事永远环绕在我脑海了
That's all I'm gonna be thinking about.
不  我没有讨厌它
No, I don't hate it.
我问你喜欢吗  你说不
I asked if you liked it, and you said no.
不喜欢和讨厌之间还差了千八百里呢
There is a lot of room between "don't like" and "hate."
米布丁与爵士乐就在这之间
You know, it's-it's where you find rice pudding and jazz.
再说  我的想法有啥所谓啊
Anyway, who cares what I think?
对我有所谓  因为你是我生命中
I do. You're the-the coolest,
最酷  最漂亮  最会打扮的人
prettiest, best-dressed person in my life.
这话本来应该算夸到天上了
Okay, that would be flattering,
可惜我知道你身边都是些什么货色
except I know all the people in your life.
听我说  艾米
Look, Amy,
我不知道该说什么了  我可能是只想到
I don't know what to say. I think I got stuck on the fact
我自己不会选那条裙子  但不该是这样
that it's not a dress I would choose, but it shouldn't be.
因为那是你的裙子
You know, it's your dress.
比如  你会嫁给莱纳德吗
I mean, hey, would you marry Leonard?
恶
Ew.
简单回答"不会"就可以了
Okay, a simple "no" would have been fine, but...
不过你懂我的意思吧
you see my point.
我们不一样
That we're different people?
没错  从现在开始  我要提醒自己
Yes, and from now on, I am gonna remember
这场婚礼你才是主角
that this wedding is all about you.
谢谢
I appreciate that.
你真是一个好伴娘
You're a good maid of honor.
博纳黛特打来了  喂
It's Bernadette. Hello?
我觉得让佩妮背黑锅  于心有愧
I feel bad about hanging Penny out to dry.
事实上  我也不喜欢那条裙子
The truth is, I don't like the dress, either.
你们在玩我吗
Are you kidding me?
现在博纳黛特也不喜欢那裙子吗
Now Bernadette doesn't like the dress?
她最贱了
Oh, she is the worst.
有人看到谢尔顿了吗
Anyone seen Sheldon?
我最后一次看到他是今早
Last time I saw Sheldon was this morning.
美国都市传说  在镜子前喊"血腥玛丽"这名字三次  就会把这个鬼给召唤来
小心  不要再念第三次他的名字了
Careful. Don't say his name a third time.
他不会真的去拉斯维加斯了吧
You don't think he actually went to Las Vegas, do you?
红色五号
Five red.
时机已到
This is it.
-你还好吗  先生  -你好
- Is everything okay, sir? ?- Oh. Hi.
不能再好了
It's better than okay.
我是个物理学家  我观察这个轮盘好久了
I am a physicist, and I have been observing this wheel for hours
并对它进行了卡方分析
and running a chi-square analysis,
发现这个球极有可能会掉在
which is how I know that the ball is far more likely
32  17  和5的位置
to land on 32, 17 or five.
希望您能暂时别更换轮盘
So if you could hold off on replacing this wheel,
我想要下几个大注了
I'd like to make several large bets.
好的  很好  鹈鹕
Well, good for you. Pelican.
鹈鹕是什么
What's pelican?
先生  请跟我们来
Sir, would you come with us? ?
不  我还没下注呢  我这是为了科学
Oh, no. I have to place my bet first. This is for science.
-黑色17号  - 不  别啊
- 17 black. - No! No!
猜猜谁终生不得再次踏入...
Oh, guess who's no longer allowed to set foot in...?
你好美
You look beautiful.
真的吗
Really?
因为我正打算退掉它
'Cause I was gonna return it.
为什么要退呢
Why would you return it?
你看起来美若一群天鹅
You look like a pile of swans.
你能喜欢  我好开心
I'm so glad you like it...
因为...这就是我的婚纱
because... it's gonna be my wedding dress.
我都等不及要娶你了
I can't wait to marry you.
你为什么一股烟味
Why do you smell like smoke?
我去维加斯了
I was in Vegas.
什么维加斯
Vegas?
抱歉  是拉斯维加斯
I'm sorry. Las Vegas.